MetaMask is a new way to connect to sites and applications.
MetaMask は をサイトとアプリケーションにつなぐ新たな方法です。
On traditional websites, a central database or bank is responsible for controlling and
従来のウェブサイト上では、中央データベース または銀行がアカウントの制御と
recovering your accounts.
回復の責任を負います。
But on MetaMask, all of the power belongs to the holder of a master key.
しかし、MetaMask 上では、全ての権限は マスターキーの保持者に属します。
Whoever holds the key, controls the accounts.
当該のキーの保持者が、アカウントを制御します。
Your secret recovery phrase is your "master key".
あなたのシークレット リカバリー フレーズ があなたの「マスターキー」です。
It's a series of 12 words that are generated when you first set up MetaMask, which allow
これは一連の 12 の単語で あなたが最初に MetaMask を設定した際に自動生成され、これにより
you to recover your wallet and funds if you ever lose access.
あなたは万が一アクセス出来なくなった場合に ウォレットと資金を復元できます。
It's important that you secure your wallet by keeping your
ウォレットの安全性を確保することは非常に重要 であり、あなたの
secret recovery phrase very safe, and very secret.
シークレット リカバリー フレーズ を非常に安全かつ秘密に保つことで実現します。
If anyone gets access to it, they will have the "master key" to your wallet and can
誰かがそれにアクセスすれば、彼らは あなたのウォレットの「マスターキー」を得て、
freely access and take all of your funds.
あなたの資金に自由にアクセスして全てを奪えます。
To secure your MetaMask wallet you'll want to safely save your secret recovery phrase.
MetaMask ウォレットの安全性を確保するため あなたは シークレット リカバリー フレーズを安全に保存したくなるでしょう。
You can write it down, hide it somewhere, put it in a safe deposit box
それを書き留めたり、どこかへ隠したり、 セーフティボックスに入れたり
or use a secure password manager.
または安全確保のためのパスワードマネジャーを使用できます。
Some users even engrave their phrase onto a metal plate!
自分たちの フレーズをメタルプレートに彫るユーザーさえいます！
Nobody, not even the team at MetaMask, can help you
何者も、 MetaMask のチームのメンバーですら、あなたが
recover your wallet if you lose your secret recovery phrase.
シークレット リカバリー フレーズを無くしたら あなたのウォレットを復元する手助けはできません。
If you haven't written down your secret recovery phrase and stored it somewhere safe,
あなたがシークレット リカバリー フレーズを書き留め安全な場所に保管していないのならば、
do it now. We'll wait.
ぜひ今それを実行してください。お待ちしております。
And remember, never share your secret recovery phrase with anyone: not even us.
さらに、あなたのシークレット リカバリー フレーズを誰とも決して共有しないことを忘れないでください。私たちでさえも。
If anyone ever asks you for it, they're trying to scam you.
それを尋ねる者がいたら、 彼らはあなたを騙そうとしているのです。
That's it!
以上です！
Now you know what a secret recovery phrase is and how to keep your wallet safe and secure.
これでシークレット リカバリ フレーズ が何であるか、あなたのウォレットと資金の安全を確保する方法が判りました。